Marcos Comelli

Front End Software Engineer

e: marcoscomelli08@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marcos-comelli/

m: +5491167922907

Summary

I've been interested in web development from a very young age. I remember myself experimenting with frontend technologies to build my first web page when I was just 14. I'm a Web Developer with a main focus on frontend but I also have considerable experience in backend. I am a very open person and always willing to try new experiences.

I finished my studies on computer engineering on 2018.

I always try to be up-to-date with the last trends and technologies to make the best apps.

Work Experience

Greencode Software (Full Stack Web Developer)

2015 - Present

Technologies:

- Frontend: Javascript, Vue.js, React, JQuery, HTML, Css, Sass, Bootstrap
- Backend: Ruby on Rails, Node.js, PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Mobile: Nativescript

Apps developed:

- + Medium like app for schools: App for sharing contents to school kids parents using Nativescript and Node.js with MongoDB on de backend
- + Bicycle races app: App for organizing bicycle races around the city made with Nativescript and Node.js with MongoDB on de backend.
- + Occupational medicine: 2 years on a project related to occupational medicine building the app with Ruby On Rails, .Net C#, PostgreSql and Testing with Rspec. Also used continuous integration and deployment. Team with 2 developers and one team leader.
- + Logistics App: 6 months building the front end of a big data app, using Vue.js with Redux and .Net on the backend. Basic usage of Docker. I was a developer in a team with 2 more developers, one team leader, a product owner and a scrum master.

Kelawar (Co-Founder)

Technologies:

- Frontend: Javascript, Vue.js, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Leaflet
- Backend: ASP.NET Core, PostgreSQL, C#, LINQ, Entity Framework
- Raspberry Pi

Currently working with a team of 5 people to build a data collection app. It aims to collect data of customers visiting a shop, so that the owner can access multiple stats about who is visiting and therefore improve their business. Get more info at <u>kelawar.com</u>

Axum (Full Stack Web Developer)

2014 - 2015

Technologies:

- Frontend: Javascript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap.
- Backend: ASP.NET Framework, SQL Server, C#, NHibernate

My team was in charge of building and maintaining an order management app. I started doing multiple front end tasks using HTML, Javascript, CSS and Grunt. Then I did various tasks on the back end with .Net MVC, C# and Ms Sql Server, such as making improvements and implementing new features. There were 5 developers in the team. We handled the version management with GIT

Personal Projects

Web page for holiday chalet renting

I built a webpage from scratch for a holiday chalet renting business that previously had zero online presence. I integrated it with a gallery so that the hole place could be viewed, as well as creating a contact form so that the potential customers could ask the owners questions and make bookings.

Key Skills

Javascript	HTML	MsSql Server	Scrum
Vue.js	Ruby On Rails	Git	Lean
CSS	Postgresql	Nativescript	

Education

Universidad Nacional de La Matanza (UNLaM)

Computer engineering (2012 - 2018)

Instituto Madero (High School)

Electronic Technician Degree

Languages

Spanish (Native) English (Cambridge First Certificate) Portuguese (Intermediate Level)